<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE pkgmetadata SYSTEM "http://www.gentoo.org/dtd/metadata.dtd">

<pkgmetadata>
<herd>no-herd</herd>
<maintainer>
	<email>doctorwhoguy@gmail.com</email>
</maintainer>
<longdescription>
Today we want to present you our latest project Pipelight, which allows to run 
your favorite Silverlight application directly inside your Linux browser. The 
project combines the effort by Erich E. Hoover with a new browser plugin that 
embeds Silverlight directly in any Linux browser supporting the Netscape Plugin 
API (Firefox, Chrome / Chromium, Midori, Opera, …). He worked on a set of Wine 
patches to get Playready DRM protected content working inside Wine and 
afterwards created an Ubuntu package called Netflix Desktop. This package 
allows one to use Silverlight inside a Windows version of Firefox, which works 
as a temporary solution but is not really user-friendly and moreover requires 
Wine to translate all API calls of the browser. To solve this problem we 
created Pipelight.

Pipelight consists out of two parts: A Linux library which is loaded into the 
browser and a Windows program started in Wine. The Windows program, called 
pluginloader.exe, simply simulates a browser and loads the Silverlight DLLs. 
When you open a page with a Silverlight application the library will send all 
commands from the browser through a pipe to the Windows process and act like a 
bridge between your browser and Silverlight. The used pipes do not have any big 
impact on the speed of the rendered video since all the video and audio data is 
not send through the pipe. Only the initialization parameters and (sometimes) 
the network traffic is send through them. As a user you will not notice anything 
from that "magic" and you can simply use Silverlight the same way as on Windows.
</longdescription>
<use>
	<flag name="binary-pluginloader">If enabled, use the upstream binary pluginloader.exe. 
		If disabled, compile your own binary; this requires a cross compiler.</flag>
	<flag name="flash">Enable Flash plugin by default.</flag>
	<flag name="foxitpdf">Enable Foxit PDF Reader plugin by default.</flag>
	<flag name="grandstream">Enable Grandstream plugin by default.</flag>
	<flag name="installation-dialogs">If enabled, you will be presented with the installation 
		dialogs of the browser plugins when they are downloaded. If disabled, Pipelight 
		will install them automatically without user intervention.</flag>
	<flag name="shockwave">Enable Shockwave plugin by default.</flag>
	<flag name="silverlight">Enable Silverlight plugin by default.</flag>
	<flag name="static">Compile a statically linked pluginloader.exe. This has no effect if 
		using the upstream binary.</flag>
	<flag name="unity3d">Enable the Unity3D plugin by default.</flag>
</use>
</pkgmetadata>
